▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 女单半决赛
高芙 6-4 6-1 贝莱克 · 赛后场上采访
You're taking on Jessica tomorrow. One
明天你要迎战杰西卡
of your best friends in the whole world.
她是你巡回赛上的挚友之一
Obviously, you two know how
你们当然都知道
to separate who's across the net.
如何区分场下朋友和隔网对手
But, a little bit of what's in store for all
但先给我们透露一点
of us tomorrow.
明天会有什么好戏
And by the way,
顺便说一句
three Americans in the finals tomorrow.
明天决赛里有三位美国球员
How cool is that?
这有多酷？
Yeah. No, it's great to, you know, see
是的 美国网球现在状态真不错
the—you know—the men. I'm just kidding.
你看看男球员们 开个玩笑
Can the men catch up?
男球员能追上来吗？
I'm just kidding.
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
真的是开玩笑
No. No.
不过说真的
Obviously,
很显然
I think American tennis is in great hands.
我觉得美国网球前景非常好
We have a lot of great guys and girls—
我们有很多优秀的男女球员
women—on both sides,
两边都有
they're all great people. And it was great
而且大家人都很好
to see Frances get to the final.
看到蒂亚福打进决赛也很棒
He's someone I think that works so hard
我觉得他一直非常努力
and definitely deserves it.
绝对配得上这个结果
And obviously Taylor, Brandon making it
弗里茨和布兰登·中岛
in the quarters and semis, and Ben winning
分别打进1/4决赛和半决赛
in Montreal.
谢尔顿则在蒙特利尔夺冠
And that's not even speaking
这还没开始说到
on the women.
女球员这边呢
Obviously Jess and me in the final.
决赛里有杰西和我
Maddie, Amanda,
还有麦迪逊和阿曼达
the list goes on and on.
名单真的太长了
So, it's pretty incredible
厉害到我甚至
that I cannot even remember all the names
都记不全此刻有多少
of how many successful Americans we have
表现出色的美国球员
in this moment.
正处在聚光灯下
But, it's definitely great
能有这样一群优秀的同伴
to be surrounded by a great group of peers
围绕在身边真的很棒
and I think we all push each other
我觉得我们彼此推动
and root for each other
也彼此为对方加油
and hopefully you guys can root for Frances
希望你们明天也能为蒂亚福
and I tomorrow.
还有我加油
We'll try to make it a double.
我们争取拿下双冠
Well, I guess it'll be a double either way
反正女单冠军肯定属于美国
on the women's, but hopefully—I love Jess.
不过我爱杰西
So, but maybe y'all can cheer
但明天你们或许也可以
for me too tomorrow.
给我多加加油
But no, Jess is—and back
说回来 杰西她……
to your original question.
回到你最初的问题
Yeah, Jess is a great person, and she's one
杰西真的是很好的人
of the people when I came on tour, one
我刚上巡回赛时
of the older players who was so nice to me
她作为资历更深的球员之一
from the beginning and it's something
从一开始就对我非常友善
that I have such mad respect for her for.
这也是我如此尊敬她的原因
And we had a tough match
我们在温网打过一场苦战
at Wimbledon, and so I'm imagining
所以我想明天
it's going to be another tough match.
也会是一场艰难的比赛
Okay, they love you here in Cincinnati,
好的 辛辛那提的观众都爱你
the heart of tennis, and you've stolen all
这里是网球之心
of our hearts.
而你赢得了我们所有人的心
Coco Gauff, everybody. Let's hear it for her.
掌声送给高芙